// Array of questions with options and correct answers
const questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Which of the following is commonly called a polyamide?",
  answer: "Nylon",
  options: [
    "Rayon",
    "Nylon",
    "Terylene",
    "Orion"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 2,
  question: "Which of the following is a force?",
  answer: "Magnetism",
  options: [
    "Heat",
    "Light",
    "Magnetism",
    "Kinetic"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 3,
  question: "The human heart is _______?",
  answer: "Myogenic Heart",
  options: [
    "Ampullary Heart",
    "Pulsating Heart",
    "Myogenic Heart",
    "Neurogenic Heart"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 4,
  question: "In context of environment, the term 'dirty dozen' refers to ____?",
  answer: "12 persistent organic pollutants",
  options: [
    "12 most harmful greenhouse gases",
    "12 ozone depleting substances",
    "12 persistent organic pollutants",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 5,
  question: "Elements which have same number of protons but different number of neutrons are called ____?",
  answer: "Isotopes",
  options: [
    "Isotopes",
    "Isomers",
    "Allotropes",
    "Allomers"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "What is the third most common gas found in the air we breathe ____?",
  answer: "Argon",
  options: [
    "Hydrogen",
    "Neon",
    "Carbon dioxide",
    "Argon"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "Which of the following type of coal has maximum carbon content?",
  answer: "Anthracite",
  options: [
    "Peat",
    "Lignite",
    "Anthracite",
    "Bituminous"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "Newton’s Third Law of Motion?",
  answer: "Every action there is an equal and opposite reaction.",
  options: [
    "Every action there is an equal and opposite reaction.",
    "Attraction or repulsion between two charges",
    "Volume of a given mass of gas increases or decreases",
    "Temperature remaining constant, volume of a given mass of gas varies inversely"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "Blood does not coagulate inside the body due to the presence of ____?",
  answer: "Heparin",
  options: [
    "Haemoglobin",
    "Fibrin",
    "Heparin",
    "Plasma"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "1 yard =____?",
  answer: "3 feet",
  options: [
    "3 feet",
    "6 feet",
    "2.4 feet",
    "12 feet"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 11,
  question: "Electric motor was invented by ____?",
  answer: "Michael Faraday",
  options: [
    "Michael Faraday",
    "Oliver Evans",
    "Thomas Edison",
    "Horace Day"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 12,
  question: "In the whole Periodic Table, which element is the most reducing agent?",
  answer: "Lithium",
  options: [
    "Chlorine",
    "Lithium",
    "Helium",
    "Neon"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 13,
  question: "The main constituent of Biogas is ____?",
  answer: "Methane",
  options: [
    "Methane",
    "Hydrogen",
    "Oxygen",
    "Carbon dioxide"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 14,
  question: "Which of the following is a nutritional deficiency disease?",
  answer: "Pellagra",
  options: [
    "Albinism",
    "Cirrhosis",
    "Rabies",
    "Pellagra"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 15,
  question: "'ELISA' test is employed to diagnose?",
  answer: "AIDS antibodies",
  options: [
    "Corona virus",
    "AIDS antibodies",
    "Tuberculosis bacterium",
    "Cancer"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 16,
  question: "Any disease or infection that is naturally transmissible from vertebrate animals to humans is called ____?",
  answer: "Zoonoses",
  options: [
    "Zonoses",
    "Zoonoses",
    "Ananoses",
    "Chordnoses"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 17,
  question: "Vitamins were discovered by ____?",
  answer: "Casimir Funk",
  options: [
    "Moseley",
    "Chadwick",
    "Frank Whittle",
    "Casimir Funk"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 18,
  question: "BCG vaccine is used to produce immunity against ____?",
  answer: "Tuberculosis",
  options: [
    "Whooping cough",
    "Tuberculosis",
    "Virus fever",
    "Smallpox"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 19,
  question: "Molasses is a byproduct of ____ Factory?",
  answer: "Sugar",
  options: [
    "Fertilizer",
    "Cotton seed oil",
    "Sugar",
    "Banaspati Ghee"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 20,
  question: "Crude Oil is heated in the furnace up to ____?",
  answer: "400°C",
  options: [
    "300°C",
    "350°C",
    "400°C",
    "450°C"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 21,
  question: "Permanent hardness of water may be removed by the addition of ____?",
  answer: "Sodium Carbonate",
  options: [
    "Sodium Carbonate",
    "Alum",
    "Potassium Permanganate",
    "Lime"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 22,
  question: "Highly intelligent Mammals are ____?",
  answer: "Dolphin",
  options: [
    "Rat",
    "Dolphin",
    "Bat",
    "Elephant"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 23,
  question: "Severe deficiency of Vitamin D results in ____?",
  answer: "Rickets",
  options: [
    "Scurvy",
    "Rickets",
    "Night blindness",
    "Osteomalacia"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 24,
  question: "The gas used in a refrigerator to cool water is ____?",
  answer: "Ammonia",
  options: [
    "Nitrogen",
    "Carbon dioxide",
    "Methane",
    "Ammonia"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 25,
  question: "CNG stands for ____?",
  answer: "Compressed Natural Gas",
  options: [
    "Converted Natural Gas",
    "Conduced Natural Gas",
    "Conducted Natural Gas",
    "Compressed Natural Gas"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 26,
  question: "The nearest planet to the Earth is ____?",
  answer: "Venus",
  options: [
    "Venus",
    "Mercury",
    "Mars",
    "Moon"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 27,
  question: "The Great Spot is on the planet ____?",
  answer: "Jupiter",
  options: [
    "Saturn",
    "Venus",
    "Mars",
    "Jupiter"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 28,
  question: "Digestion of food is completed in the ____?",
  answer: "Small intestine",
  options: [
    "Small intestine",
    "Large intestine",
    "Stomach",
    "Liver"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 29,
  question: "The good sources of Vitamin-C are ____?",
  answer: "Fresh vegetables and fruits",
  options: [
    "Green leafy vegetables",
    "Seeds",
    "Fresh vegetables and fruits",
    "Sea foods"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 30,
  question: "In general, wind speed of 10–13 kph causes ____?",
  answer: "Minor or no damage",
  options: [
    "Minor or no damage",
    "Considerable damage",
    "Severe damage",
    "Extreme damage"
  ]
}
];
